Say yes.
Marry Me is a romance, comedy, music film directed by Kat Coiro.
After finding out about her fiancé's cheating ways, a pop
superstar impulsively marries a total stranger.
They must soon decide if two people from such
different worlds can find true love.
Kat Valdez, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Charlie Gilbert, played by Owen Wilson.
Bastian, played by Maluma.
Colin, played by John Bradley.
Parker Debbs, played by Sarah Silverman.
Lou Gilbert, played by Chloe Coleman.
Marry Me is a 2022 American romantic comedy drama film
starring Jennifer Lopez, Owen Wilson, and Maluma.
Superstar Kat Valdez (Lopez) decides to marry Charlie Gilbert (Wilson), a math teacher holding a "Marry Me"
sign, after learning that her on-stage bridegroom, Bastian (Maluma), has been having an affair.
It is directed by Kat Coiro based on a screenplay by
John Rogers, Tami Sagher, and Harper Dill.
Based on the 2012 webcomic of the same title by Bobby Crosby.
The film was announced in April 2019, with Lopez and Wilson set to
star and Coiro joining the project as director.
Universal Pictures acquired the film distribution rights in July 2019.
Principal photography took place in Manhattan in October and November 2019.
A soundtrack album of the same name by Lopez and Maluma was also produced.
The lead single, titled "Pa' Ti", was released on September 24, 2020, and debuted at number nine on
Billboard's Hot Latin Songs, marking Lopez's highest chart debut in the United States since 2017.
Marry Me premiered in Los Angeles on February 9, 2022, and was released in the United States
theatrically and simultaneously available on Peacock Premium on February 11.
It was delayed twice from an original February 2021
release date due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
The film received positive reviews from critics, grossing
$56.5 million against a budget of $23 million.
On streaming, Marry Me became the most-streamed day-and-date title on Peacock.
The film explores themes of marriage, celebrity, based
on comic, wedding, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.